export const verbPracticeDataEspanol = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Yo", answer: "soy" },
    { prompt: "Tú", answer: "eres" },
    { prompt: "Él", answer: "es" },
    { prompt: "Ella", answer: "es" },
    { prompt: "Eso", answer: "es" },
    { prompt: "soy", answer: "yo" },
    { prompt: "eres", answer: "tú" },
    { prompt: "es", answer: "él/ella/eso" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Yo", answer: "tengo" },
    { prompt: "Tú", answer: "tienes" },
    { prompt: "Él", answer: "tiene" },
    { prompt: "Ella", answer: "tiene" },
    { prompt: "tengo", answer: "yo" },
    { prompt: "tienes", answer: "tú" },
    { prompt: "tiene", answer: "él/ella" }
  ]
};
